<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>

    <!-- Help topics. These are fairly common. -->

    <string name="helptopic_titlepage_title">Welcome to Atomic!</string>
    <string name="helptopic_titlepage_body">
        <![CDATA[
        <p>Welcome to Atomic, a fork of yaaic. This guide will fill you in on what\'s changed or what\'s new.</p>
        <p>If this was included in your ROM, please consider buying me a beer! Check out the project page at</p>
        <p><a href="https://github.com/indrora/atomic">https://github.com/indrora/atomic</a></p>
        <p>I depend on you to provide me with feedback!</p>
        ]]>
    </string>

    <string name="helptopic_introduction_title">Introduction</string>
    <string name="helptopic_introduction_body">
        <![CDATA[
			<p>Atomic is a fork of yaaic by Sebasian Kaspari under the GPLv3 license.</p>
			<p>Many things have changed since the initial fork. This guide will show you some of the things that have changed between yaaic and Atomic.</p>
        	<p>Several large changes have happened that stand out from the rest.</p>
        	<img src="nick_complete.png" />
        	<p>A button has been added for nick completion. This is availible to all users, not just ones without physical search keys.</p>
        	<img src="event_icons.png" />
        	<p>Nearly every icon and graphic has been revamped using the Holo style from Google.</p>
        	<img src="smileys.png" />
        	<p>Smileys and other features are still there, however.</p>
        ]]>
    </string>

    <string name="helptopic_colorschemes_title">Color schemes</string>
    <string name="helptopic_colorschemes_body"><![CDATA[
        <p>Atomic features a selection of color schemes. There are a wide selection of schemes, the majority based on the Base16 color schemes from Chris Kempson.</p>
        <p>If you are coming from a previous release of Atomic, your color scheme will be reverted to the default.</p>
        <p>A selection of the color schemes available</p>
        
        <img src="colorschemes.png" />
        <p>All color schemes have two variants: Dark and Light. AMOLED users may find it adventageous to use the dark style, as it will conserve power.</p>
    	]]>
    </string>

    <string name="helptopic_notification_title">Status Notification</string>
    <string name="helptopic_notification_body">
        <![CDATA[
        <p>Atomic features, like other clients, a status notification, showing the ways that you may be highlighted or contacted in a channel.</p>
    	<img src="notification_icon.png" />
    ]]>
    </string>

    <string name="helptopic_conversation_title">Channels and servers</string>
    <string name="helptopic_conversation_body">
    <![CDATA[
        <p>Atomic has two options for displaying the current channel. These are showing the channels as a bar (the default), which looks like this:</p>
        <img src="channel_as_bar.png" />
        <p>Optionally, you can turn off the channel bar and know only about the currently visible channel:</p>
        <img src="channel_as_subtitle.png" />
        <p>These settings may be found in the &quot;Interface&quot; section of the settings.</p>
    ]]>
    </string>
    <string name="helptopic_reconnect_title">Network awareness</string>
    <string name="helptopic_reconnect_body">
        <![CDATA[
        <p><em>New in 1.17</em></p>
		<p>Connections will automatically re-connect themselves when your mobile or wifi network breaks down.</p>
		<p>Optionally, you may automatically reconnect your networks when you move between wifi and mobile networks</p>
		<p>The classic behavior is kept for posterity. It may vanish in later releases.</p>
        ]]>
    </string>
</resources>
